Guide to the John M. Meek Collection
John M. Meek Collection 1934-1999 1967-1968
PP/068
Meek, John M.
5.50
Carl Albert Center Congressional and Political Collections 630 Parrington Oval, Room 202B Norman, OK, 73019-4031 URL: http://cacarchives.ou.edu Email: cacarchives@ou.edu Phone: 405-325-6372 Fax: 405-325-6419
Biographical Information:
A native Oklahoman of Choctaw ancestry, John Martin Meek was one of the most successful public relations counselors in the Washington, D.C., area from 1969 to his relocation to Arizona in 1999. Following high school graduation, he served in the U.S. Navy and saw action during the Korean Conflict. After completing his military career, he attended the University of Oklahoma and graduated with a degree in journalism in 1958. He also received a master's degree from Syracuse University. During his newspaper career, he worked on newspapers in Oklahoma, Texas, and New York. In 1959, he became manager of the Community Development Department for the U.S. Junior Chamber of Commerce. Following the election of President John F. Kennedy, Meek moved to Washington where he served as press secretary to U.S. Senator Robert S. Kerr of Oklahoma. Following Kerr's unexpected death in 1963, he held the same position with Senator J. Howard Edmondson who was appointed to succeed Kerr.
During the 1964 Democratic National Convention, Meek was the assistant to the publicity director. In 1965, he held a similar position for the presidential inaugural. Shortly thereafter, he moved to the Democratic National Committee (DNC) and served as the director of congressional relations. As the chief liaison between the DNC and all Democratic members of Congress, he was involved in numerous activities related to the day-to-day operations of congressional offices. He became coordinator for the 1968 Democratic National Convention held in Chicago. In this position, he was responsible for many of the arrangements necessary for conducting the event.
Following the convention, he became a public relations counselor in Washington, D.C. During his years in the nation's capital, he was involved in numerous projects. In the late 1980s, he served as the counselor to the state of Arizona in its quest to become the site of the Superconducting Super Collider. He also worked on major national public education programs in health care for Glaxo Wellcome.
Since 1999, Meek has lived in Tucson, Arizona, where he continues to write and consult. He also is an adjunct professor at Pima Community College. His first novel, The Christmas Hour, is slated for publication in late 2002.
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Topical Term:
Clinton, Bill, 1946---Inauguration, 1993; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973--Inauguration; Political campaigns--United States; Political conventions--United States
Administrative Information
Arrangement of Materials:
This collection contains 4 series: Manuscripts, Oversize, Maps, and Photographs. The Manuscripts series is arranged alphabetically then chronologically by year, month, and day. The Oversized series is arranged into two groups: three-dimensional ephemera, paper ephemera. The Photographs series is arranged generally by year and grouped by event or content.
Scope and Contents
The John M. Meek Collection is a small collection which includes material on aspects of the organization of the 1968 Democratic National Convention, from hotel accommodations to first aid and security to requests from committees and entertainers to appear at the convention. While there is a copy of the proceedings of the convention, there is little else in the papers that relates to the event as it occurred. Most materials concern preliminary preparations for the convention. A small photograph collection is also included in the collection.
Detailed List of Contents
- Manuscripts, 1934-1999; id1099756; CAC_PP_068_1_0000_0000_0000
  - Chicago, International Amphitheatre, undated, 1951, 1967; id1099758; CAC_PP_068_1_1_1_0000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Correspondence: convention facilities; Chicago's bid agreements; data.
  - Chicago, International Amphitheatre, 1968; id1099759; CAC_PP_068_1_1_2_0000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Correspondence: convention facilities.
  - Clippings, 1948, 1963, 1966; id1099760; CAC_PP_068_1_1_3_0000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Election
  - Clippings, 1967; id1099761; CAC_PP_068_1_1_4_0000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Site selection, Chicago.
  - Clippings, 1968-1969; id1099762; CAC_PP_068_1_1_5_0000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Convention; platform; protest threats.
  - Correspondence, General, 1968; id1099763; CAC_PP_068_1_1_6_0000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Convention dates, requests.
  - Correspondence, Political, 1968; id1099764; CAC_PP_068_1_1_7_0000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Candidates; civil liberties; Vietnam; Democratic Party platform; protesters, national anthem.
  - Credentials, Press, 1967-1968; id1099765; CAC_PP_068_1_1_8_0000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Requests for press credentials. 1967-May 1968
  - Credentials, Press, June-Aug., 1968; id1099766; CAC_PP_068_1_1_9_0000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Requests for press credentials.
  - Delegates and Alternates, 1968; id1099767; CAC_PP_068_1_1_10_0000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Lists of state delegates and alternates.
  - Democratic National Committee, 1956, 1960-1966; id1099768; CAC_PP_068_1_1_11_0000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    List of committee chairmen; telephone numbers of state delegations' headquarters; account information.
  - Democratic National Committee, 1967; id1099769; CAC_PP_068_1_1_12_0000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Call for meetings; lists of committee members; speech (unknown speaker); dinner invitations to committee members; committee member schedules; committee member reservations; committee meeting minutes.
  - Democratic National Committee, Jan.-May, 1968; id1099770; CAC_PP_068_1_1_13_0000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Speech by John M. Bailey; allotted votes and delegates per state delegation; reservations for committee meetings; meeting agendas; schedules and calendars; committee resolutions; activity reports by John M. Meek; biographical sketch of John M. Meek.
  - Democratic National Committee, June-Sept., 1968; id1099771; CAC_PP_068_1_1_14_0000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Chicago students and volunteer participation; proclamation from Chicago Sun-Times, Chicago Daily News; correspondence with state delegates; receipts; committee accounts with hotels; United Democrats for Humphrey; possible demonstrations; statement by Sen. Eugene McCarthy; Booklet: Temporary Roll of Delegates and Alternates to the Democratic National Convention.
  - Democratic National Committee, Committee on Credentials, 1963-1964, 1968; id1099772; CAC_PP_068_1_1_15_0000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Credentials, design; convention badges; minority reports on Credentials Committee; list of Democratic congressmen; Credentials Committee and civil rights.
  - Democratic National Committee, Headquarters, 1967-1968; id1099773; CAC_PP_068_1_1_16_0000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Bills; receipts; and account information.
  - Democratic National Committee, Media Conference, 1963-1964, 1967; id1099774; CAC_PP_068_1_1_17_0000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Media requirements for coverage of convention; agenda for the meeting of representatives of the news media and communications services; schedule of conference.
  - Democratic National Committee, Media Conference, Stenographic Report, 1967; id1099775; CAC_PP_068_1_1_18_0000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Report of the proceedings of December 7, 1967.
  - Democratic National Committee, Memos, 1968; id1099776; CAC_PP_068_1_1_19_0000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Memos concerning work space and housing, delegations, volunteers, new staff; John Meek's activities; information and suggestions on office services; convention identification and tickets.
  - Democratic National Committee, Press Releases, 1963-1964, 1967-1968; id1099777; CAC_PP_068_1_1_20_0000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Press releases concerning the allocation of delegates; Chicago convention site; street crime; Lyndon B. Johnson. (1967-July 1968).
  - Democratic National Committee, Press Releases, Aug.-Sept, 1968; id1099778; CAC_PP_068_1_1_21_0000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Headquarter space for candidates; work space and housing; convention session schedules; Carl Albert; Chicago host committee.
  - Democratic National Committee, Site Committee, [1967]; id1099779; CAC_PP_068_1_1_22_0000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Travel reservations for Site Committee; lists of committee members; committee reports.
  - Democratic National Committee, Site Committee, 1967; id1099780; CAC_PP_068_1_1_23_0000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Arrangements for meetings; schedule of Site Selection Committee meeting; Committee travel schedules.
  - Democratic National Committee, Site Committee, Meeting Transcript, 1967; id1099781; CAC_PP_068_1_1_24_0000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Meeting of April 11, 1967.
  - Democratic Party Platform Committee, 1967-1968; id1099783; CAC_PP_068_1_2_1_0000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Requests by organizations to appear before the committee, including American Congress for Irish Freedom, National Federation of Independent Business, National Council on Crime and Delinquency, National Association of Life Underwriters, and Veterans of Foreign Wars; correspondence concerning a bill of rights for victims of crime and electoral college reform; work space for committee; lists of committee members. (1967-Mar. 1968)
  - Democratic Party Platform Committee, May-Aug, 1968; id1099784; CAC_PP_068_1_2_2_0000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Requests by organizations to appear before the committee, including Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, National Council of the Churches of Christ, National Federation of Settlements and Neighborhood Centers, American Israel Public Affairs Committee, National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, Association of American Medical Colleges, Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace, Paralyzed Veterans of America, Inc., National Canners Association, Sierra Club, National Federation of Federal Employees, Federation of American Scientists; correspondence from World Association of Mothers for Peace, Inc.; Carl Albert; public hearings; meeting schedules; copy of the 1968 platform of the Democratic Party.
  - Employment and Appointment, 1967-1968; id1099785; CAC_PP_068_1_2_3_0000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Correspondence asking for work or appointment at the Democratic National Convention. Referrals included.
  - Entertainment and Convention Program, 1964, 1967-1968; id1099786; CAC_PP_068_1_2_4_0000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Correspondence concerning musical entertainment, honorary speakers, fireworks; 1964 Democratic National Convention Program; requests to add special events to program. (1967-Mar. 1968)
  - Entertainment and Convention Program, Apr.-Aug., 1968; id1099787; CAC_PP_068_1_2_5_0000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Correspondence concerning musical entertainment, honorary attendees, special events. Among the correspondents are Charles C. Diggs and John Conyers.
  - Food, 1968; id1099788; CAC_PP_068_1_2_6_0000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Correspondence concerning arrangements for food service at convention.
  - Illinois Bell Telephone Company, Strike, 1968; id1099789; CAC_PP_068_1_2_7_0000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Telephone requirements for Democratic National Committee at Hilton Hotel; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers strike.
  - Insurance, 1967-1968; id1099790; CAC_PP_068_1_2_8_0000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Insurance requirements at the International Amphitheatre.
  - Media, 1967-1968; id1099791; CAC_PP_068_1_2_9_0000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    Lighting, sound, and basic facilities for convention and press.
  - Novelties, 1952, 1964, 1967-1968; id1099792; CAC_PP_068_1_2_10_0000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Correspondence concerning miscellaneous items that were produced solely for the convention, including posters, buttons, ribbons, dress for pages; purple badge from the 1952 Democratic National Convention for the Assistant Sergeant At Arms.
  - Office Equipment and Furnishings, Decoration and Services, undated, 1964, 1967-1968; id1099793; CAC_PP_068_1_2_11_0000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Correspondence from companies offering services and products; lists of requirements; orders from companies. (1967-1968 Jan.)
  - Office Equipment and Furnishings, Decoration and Services, Feb.-May, 1968; id1099794; CAC_PP_068_1_2_12_0000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Correspondence from companies offering services and products; orders from companies.
  - Office Equipment and Furnishings, Decoration and Services, June-Aug, 1968; id1099795; CAC_PP_068_1_2_13_0000 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Press, 1967-1968; id1099796; CAC_PP_068_1_2_14_0000 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    Convention press kit; correspondence concerning coverage of convention from United Press, International, Life, Chicago Sun-Times, and WGN.
  - Seating Arrangements, undated, 1956, 1960, 1967-1968; id1099797; CAC_PP_068_1_2_15_0000 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    Correspondence concerning seating at Amphitheatre.
  - Security, undated, 1964, 1966-1968; id1099798; CAC_PP_068_1_2_16_0000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Correspondence concerning the responsibility of Democratic National Committee and the city of Chicago concerning security; various security companies offering their services and products; turnstiles; fencing; identification; tickets; arrangements for "security rooms" for the President, Vice-President, and Sen. Eugene McCarthy; riot control issues; Timothy Leary; Allen Ginsberg; Hippies; Yippies; Black Panthers; statement from Richard J. Daley.
  - Site Selection, Houston, 1966-1967; id1099799; CAC_PP_068_1_2_17_0000 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Correspondence, maps, and proposals dealing with the Site Selection Committee meeting in Houston to explore the possibility of Houston for the 1968 Democratic National Convention; list of persons "instrumental in hosting the Democratic Site Committee" visit; committee itinerary. (1966-April 1967)
  - Site Selection, Houston, May-Oct., 1967; id1099800; CAC_PP_068_1_2_18_0000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Correspondence, maps, and proposals dealing with the Site Selection Committee meeting to explore the possibility of Houston as the site for the 1968 Democratic National Convention.
  - Site Selection, Las Vegas, 1967; id1099801; CAC_PP_068_1_2_19_0000 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Correspondence and invitations dealing with the Site Selection Committee meeting to explore the possibility of Las Vegas as the site for the 1968 Democratic National Convention; correspondents include Howard W. Cannon and Alan Bible.
  - Site Selection, Los Angeles, 1967; id1099802; CAC_PP_068_1_2_20_0000 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    Correspondence, maps, plans, and proposals dealing with the Site Selection Committee meeting to explore the possibility of Los Angeles as the site for the 1968 Democratic National Convention; resolution from the County of Los Angeles Board of Supervisors to invite the convention to Los Angeles; correspondents include Sam Yorty, mayor of Los Angeles
  - Site Selection, Miami Beach, 1966-1967; id1099803; CAC_PP_068_1_2_21_0000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    Correspondence, plans, and proposals dealing with the Site Selection Committee meeting to explore the possibility of Miami Beach as the site for the 1968 Democratic National Convention; issue of state of Florida being placed under professional sanctions by the Florida Education Association and the National Education Association; correspondents include Charles E. Bennett and Claude R. Kirk, Jr. (governor of Florida).
  - Speeches/ Proceedings, Compilation (1 of 5), 1968; id1099804; CAC_PP_068_1_2_22_0000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    Compilation of speeches and proceedings made at the convention.
  - Speeches/Proceedings, Compilation (2 of 5), 1968; id1099805; CAC_PP_068_1_2_23_0000 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Speeches/Proceedings, Compilation (3 of 5), 1968; id1099806; CAC_PP_068_1_2_24_0000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Speeches/Proceedings, Compilation (4 of 5), 1968; id1099807; CAC_PP_068_1_2_25_0000 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Speeches/Proceedings, Compilation (5 of 5), 1968; id1099808; CAC_PP_068_1_2_26_0000 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Tickets, Printing, 1968; id1099809; CAC_PP_068_1_2_27_0000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Proposals from ticket printing services; example of convention ticket.
  - Tickets and Passes, 1967; id1099810; CAC_PP_068_1_2_28_0000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    Correspondence dealing with requests for tickets and passes.
  - Tickets and Passes, Jan.-Mar., 1968; id1099812; CAC_PP_068_1_3_1_0000 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tickets and Passes, Apr., 1968; id1099813; CAC_PP_068_1_3_2_0000 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tickets and Passes, May, 1968; id1099814; CAC_PP_068_1_3_3_0000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tickets and Passes, June, 1968; id1099815; CAC_PP_068_1_3_4_0000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Tickets and Passes, July, 1968; id1099816; CAC_PP_068_1_3_5_0000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tickets and Passes, Aug., 1968; id1099817; CAC_PP_068_1_3_6_0000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Transportation, 1964, 1967-1968; id1099818; CAC_PP_068_1_3_7_0000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Correspondence dealing with transportation for the convention; possible transit strikes; American Airlines; group travel accommodations; baggage tags; VIP transportation; staff cars.
  - Volunteers, Legal and Medical, 1968; id1099819; CAC_PP_068_1_3_8_0000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Correspondence dealing with professionals who wanted to volunteer their legal or medical skills during the convention.
  - Volunteers, Pages, 1967-1968; id1099820; CAC_PP_068_1_3_9_0000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Correspondence dealing with individuals who wanted to volunteer their time as pages at the convention.
  - Volunteers, Guards, Ushers and General Volunteers, 1967-1968; id1099821; CAC_PP_068_1_3_10_0000 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Correspondence dealing with individuals who wanted to volunteer their time as guards, ushers or other unspecified volunteer positions at the convention.
  - Women and Minorities, 1968; id1099822; CAC_PP_068_1_3_11_0000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Correspondence concerning the rights of women and minorities in the Democratic Party Platform and Convention; Mississippi delegation; convention activities for "the wives" and scheduled "women's activities"; government programs and minorities; underprivileged.; press release by Democratic National Committee about the attendance of African-American delegates; correspondents include Betty Friedan, president of the National Organization for Women.
  - Work Space and Housing, undated, 1967; id1099823; CAC_PP_068_1_3_12_0000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Correspondence and requests for work space and housing; includes delegations, Democratic National Committee, the press, and individuals.
  - Work Space and Housing, Jan.-Mar, 1968; id1099824; CAC_PP_068_1_3_13_0000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Work Space and Housing, Apr.-May, 1968; id1099825; CAC_PP_068_1_3_14_0000 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Work Space and Housing, June 4-21, 1968; id1099826; CAC_PP_068_1_3_15_0000 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Work Space and Housing, June 24-28, 1968; id1099827; CAC_PP_068_1_3_16_0000 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Work Space and Housing, July, 1968; id1099828; CAC_PP_068_1_3_17_0000 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Work Space and Housing, Aug, 1968; id1099829; CAC_PP_068_1_3_18_0000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Youth, 1967-1968; id1099830; CAC_PP_068_1_3_19_0000 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Correspondence dealing with Young Democrats, foreign students and youth groups at the Convention; schedule of youth activities.
  - Democratic National Convention, Contract, 1968; id1099831; CAC_PP_068_1_3_20_0000 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Materials in Folders 20-25 were donated to the Carl Albert Center in the Summer of 2009 by John M. Meek.
  - Democratic National Convention, Speeches, 1968; id1099832; CAC_PP_068_1_3_21_0000 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Includes vice presidential acceptance speech by Edmund S. Muskie titled "Working for Freedom" and presidential acceptance speech by Hubert H. Humphrey titled "A New Day for America." Materials in Folders 20-25 were donated to the Carl Albert Center in the Summer of 2009 by John M. Meek.
  - Democratic National Convention, Telephone Numbers, 1968; id1099833; CAC_PP_068_1_3_22_0000 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., Miscellaneous, 1964-1965, 1978, 1999; id1099834; CAC_PP_068_1_3_23_0000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Includes One Nation, One People: Democratic Platform, 1964; press kit for the Inaugural Committee, 1965; official inaugural program, January 20, 1965; The Democrat, April-May 1968; and Among Friends of LBJ, April 30, 1999. Materials in Folders 20-25 were donated to the Carl Albert Center in the Summer of 2009 by John M. Meek.
  - Meek, John, Miscellaneous, undated, 1968; id1099835; CAC_PP_068_1_3_24_0000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    Includes biographical sketch and notes written after the 1968 Democratic National Convention. Materials in Folders 20-25 were donated to the Carl Albert Center in the Summer of 2009 by John M. Meek.
  - Republican National Convention, 1967-1968; id1099836; CAC_PP_068_1_3_25_0000 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    Includes contract with the city of Miami Beach, Florida; and badges for convention. Materials in Folders 20-25 were donated to the Carl Albert Center in the Summer of 2009 by John M. Meek.
- Oversized, 1934-1999; id1099837; CAC_PP_068_2_0000_0000_0000
  Boxes 4, 5, and 6 were donated to the Carl Albert Center in the Summer of 2009 by John M. Meek
  - Honored Guest Badge (2), 1968; id1099839; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_1 (Box 4)
    Democratic National Convention.
  - Newsreel Badge, 1952; id1099840; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_2 (Box 4)
  - Page Badge (2, 1964; id1099841; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_3 (Box 4)
  - Honored Guest Badge, 1964; id1099842; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_4 (Box 4)
  - Western Union Badge, 1952; id1099843; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_5 (Box 4)
  - Assistant Sergeant at Arms Badge, 1956; id1099844; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_6 (Box 4)
  - Delegate Key, 1968; id1099845; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_7 (Box 4)
  - Tie Tacks (3) and Cuff Links (2 sets), [undated]; id1099846; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_8 (Box 4)
  - Bracelets (3), [undated]; id1099847; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_9 (Box 4)
  - Tie Tacks (4) with name "Shapiro.", [undated]; id1099848; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_10 (Box 4)
  - Assistant Sergeant at Arms Badge, 1952; id1099849; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_11 (Box 4)
  - Souvenir Coins (2), 1968; id1099850; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_12 (Box 4)
    Celebrating the Illinois Sesquicentennial in 1968.
  - Oklahoma Bumper Stickers, [undated]; id1099851; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_13 (Box 4)
  - Tickets to the 1956 Democratic National Convention, id1099852; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_14 (Box 4)
  - Tickets to the 1964 Democratic National Convention, id1099853; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_15 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Press Badges, 1964; id1099854; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_16 (Box 4)
  - Ticket and Press Badge, 1972; id1099855; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_17 (Box 4)
  - Badge for the United Democrats for Humphrey, 1968; id1099856; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_18 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Page and Staff Tickets, 1968; id1099857; CAC_PP_068_2_4_0000_19 (Box 4)
  - Plastic Tote Bags (2), 1968; id1099859; CAC_PP_068_2_5_0000_1 (Box 5)
  - Notebook with Donkey Caricature., [undated]; id1099860; CAC_PP_068_2_5_0000_2 (Box 5)
  - Evening Star [Washington, D.C.] January 20, 1965; id1099862; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_1 (Box 6)
    focus on the inauguration of Lyndon B. Johnson.
  - Astrodome, 1966; id1099863; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_2 (Box 6)
    commemorative program.
  - 1964 Democratic National Convention, id1099864; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_3 (Box 6)
  - Democrats in Convention 1972, id1099865; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_4 (Box 6)
  - Democratic National Convention 1968 Chicago, id1099866; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_5 (Box 6)
  - Look, December 31, 1963; id1099867; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_6 (Box 6)
  - Life, July 5, 1968; id1099868; CAC_PP_068_2_6_0000_7 (Box 6)
- Maps, 1934-1999; id1099869; CAC_PP_068_3_0000_0000_0000
  - id1099870 (Folder 1)